{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a policy framework that allows domain owners to specify how email receivers should handle emails that fail authentication checks?",
      "options": ["DKIM", "SPF", "PEM", "DMARC"],
      "correct_answers": ["DMARC"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to an authentication method that enables the signing of an outbound email message with a digital signature?",
      "options": ["SPF", "DKIM", "DMARC", "PEM"],
      "correct_answers": ["DKIM"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to an email authentication mechanism that allows domain owners to specify which IP addresses are authorized to send emails on behalf of their domain?",
      "options": ["DMARC", "PEM", "DKIM", "SPF"],
      "correct_answers": ["SPF"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a cryptographic standard (and a file format) used for the storage and transmission of private keys in email communications?",
      "options": ["PEM", "DMARC", "SPF", "DKIM"],
      "correct_answers": ["PEM"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following solutions would be the best choice for real-time protection against spam and phishing attacks?",
      "options": ["Email client filter", "Host-based AV software", "Email security gateway", "Cloud-based email service"],
      "correct_answers": ["Email security gateway"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to the process of maintaining the integrity of files and data?",
      "options": ["DLP", "SIEM", "FIM", "SHA"],
      "correct_answers": ["FIM"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a solution that helps organizations mitigate risks associated with data breaches, insider threats, and compliance violations?",
      "options": ["EDR", "DLP", "IAM", "UTM"],
      "correct_answers": ["DLP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Network Access Control (NAC) defines a set of rules enforced in a network that the clients attempting to access the network must comply with. NAC can be implemented with agent software (permanent or dissolvable) or agentless by an external device.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a security solution that provides the capability for detection, analysis, response, and real-time monitoring of cyber threats at the device level?",
      "options": ["SWG", "CASB", "EDR", "NGFW"],
      "correct_answers": ["EDR"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a cybersecurity approach that focuses on recognizing and addressing potential threats originating from multiple sources?",
      "options": ["XDR", "WAF", "EDR", "SWG"],
      "correct_answers": ["XDR"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a cybersecurity approach aimed at identifying insider threats, compromised accounts, or malicious activity?",
      "options": ["Threat intelligence", "User behavior analytics", "Security policies and procedures", "Defense in depth"],
      "correct_answers": ["User behavior analytics"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a framework for managing access control to digital resources?",
      "options": ["PAM", "SSO", "IAM", "MFA"],
      "correct_answers": ["IAM"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the terms listed below is used to describe the technical process of removing a user's access to an organization's systems and resources?",
      "options": ["De-provisioning", "Group Policy", "IAM", "Offboarding"],
      "correct_answers": ["De-provisioning"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A general characteristic of a standard user account is that it provides access to basic system resources but does not allow the user to make system changes.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "An authentication subsystem in which a single set of authentication credentials provides access to multiple systems across different organizations or security domains is referred to as:",
      "options": ["Syndication", "Federation", "Association", "Propagation"],
      "correct_answers": ["Federation"]
    },
    {
      "question": "An authentication subsystem that enables a user to access multiple, connected system components after a single login on one component is known as:",
      "options": ["NAC", "SSO", "AAA", "MFA"],
      "correct_answers": ["SSO"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a protocol designed for accessing and managing information related to user accounts, groups, devices, and other resources within an organization?",
      "options": ["SOAP", "RDP", "LDAP", "SAML"],
      "correct_answers": ["LDAP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "OAuth is an open standard for:",
      "options": ["Auditing", "Authentication", "Authorization", "Attestation"],
      "correct_answers": ["Authorization"]
    },
    {
      "question": "OpenID Connect is a protocol used for:",
      "options": ["Attestation", "Authorization", "Auditing", "Authentication"],
      "correct_answers": ["Authentication"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A common implementation of identity and access controls in federated SSO systems uses OpenID Connect and OAuth 2.0 together to provide authentication and authorization services.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the characteristic features of SAML? (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Enables only the exchange of SSO authorization data",
        "Handles both authentication and authorization for SSO",
        "Uses XML for data exchange",
        "Commonly used in enterprise environments and legacy systems",
        "Enables only the exchange of SSO authentication data",
        "Uses JSON for data exchange",
        "Specifically designed for web and mobile applications"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Handles both authentication and authorization for SSO",
        "Uses XML for data exchange",
        "Commonly used in enterprise environments and legacy systems"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the terms listed below refers to the process of confirming the integrity and compliance status of various components such as devices, software, configurations, and user privileges?",
      "options": ["Attestation", "Authentication", "Auditing", "Authorization"],
      "correct_answers": ["Attestation"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refer(s) to the Mandatory Access Control (MAC) model? (Select all that apply)",
      "options": [
        "Users are not allowed to change access policies at their own discretion",
        "Labels and clearance levels can only be applied and changed by an administrator",
        "Every object has an owner who can determine permissions",
        "Access to resources based on user identity",
        "Every resource has a sensitivity label matching a clearance level assigned to a user"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Users are not allowed to change access policies at their own discretion",
        "Labels and clearance levels can only be applied and changed by an administrator",
        "Every resource has a sensitivity label matching a clearance level assigned to a user"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Discretionary Access Control (DAC) is an access control model based on user identity. In DAC, every object has an owner who at their own discretion determines what kind of permissions other users can have for that object.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of control access model connects user permissions to their specific responsibilities?",
      "options": ["DAC", "RBAC", "MAC", "ABAC"],
      "correct_answers": ["RBAC"]
    }
  ]
}